adlandpro.com 2016-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: October 18, 2012 

The privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [AdlandPro.com](http://www.adlandpro.com/). 

AdlandPro.com, owned and operated by Softfornet Solutions Ltd., agrees to abide by this Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on web pages hosted by Adlandpro.com 

The terms "we" and "us" refer to [AdlandPro.com](http://www.adlandpro.com/). 

Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

Softfornet Solutions Ltd. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this web site, www.adlandpro.com. 

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@adlandpro.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected on the AdlandPro.com web site, or submitted to AdlandPro.com at any time through any web pages which we host. 

Personally Identifiable Information - When visiting AdlandPro.com's or any Affiliate's web site and signing up for or using AdlandPro.com services through a web page hosted by us, you may choose to supply AdlandPro.com with information that identifies you personally. For **end-users** , this information may include your name and contact information, gender, age group, occupation and industry, and user-comments and opt-in preference; we intend to collect billing information, which may, in the future, include credit card numbers, and other payment types of information. We also intend to collect behavior patterns, which may include recording frequency of use of our services, which and when items were purchased, at which site and page, and other information related to behavior patterns. We collect **prospect** information, which may include name, and contact information of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services. For **Affiliates** , the information we collect may include your name and contact information, your site's category, your web site information (URL), and user-comments. 

When Affiliates add our services to their web site, end-user information collected is stored in our database. Thus, our database has information collected on our site as well as on Affiliate sites. The information AdlandPro.com collects will be used as stated below. **As for each of our Affiliates, they will determine** what they will do with the information collected. 

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as advertising, search engine submissions, etc., completing an order, shipping a product, or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Affiliates and end-users. 

When we receive subscribed email addresses or get messages posted on our support forum, we use the return email addresses to reply with the information requested. For **subscribed email addresses** , we will email with service announcements and updates as requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

For **end-users** , when supplying name and contact information, shipping information, prospect information, and user-comments to AdlandPro.com, we will use it to answer your questions, ship your products, or provide you with the requested services. 

For **prospects** , when getting information about you, we will use the information for which it was intended or submitted. You have the right to access and correct information submitted about you, receive the same courteous and professional treatment and services as our end-users and Affiliates. 

Finally, for **end-users** , **Affiliates** , and **prospects** , we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. You may opt-out of any of any of these emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at support@adlandpro.com. 

Service Providers 

We may provide your personally identifiable information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

Legal Disclaimer 

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information: 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if AdlandPro.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

## Conditional Access Statistics Screen

AdlandPro.com maintains an area called the "Statistics Screen" which is an admin tool that allows you to track your promotion provided by AdlandPro.com. To access the "Statistics Screen", you will need to enter an account ID and password. In order to sign up for an account, you will need to provide your name and contact information, your site's category, your web site information (URL, visitors per day, description of services offered at web site), etc. 

## How You Can Access, Correct or Delete Your Information

For **Affiliate/End User** , you can access all your personally identifiable information that AdlandPro.com collects online and maintains by logging into your password-protected account at http://www.AdlandPro.com and selecting to update your "Profile." If you do not currently have an account with us, and have submitted information on our site, you can access and correct the information that we maintain by contacting us [here](http://www.adlandpro.com/contactus.aspx). You may also request to delete your information or deactivate your account with us by sending us an email at support@adlandpro.com. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

A public profile will be created when opening an account on AdlandPro.com. To edit your privacy settings please go to the My Account settings page, options tab and adjust your options for privacy settings. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Public Ads

Our web site offers publicly accessible ads. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from an ad please edit the posting. In some cases, if you request removal of an ad, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

## Tracking Technologies / Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. Session cookies are used to enable persistence of user logged in status when navigating through our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies are used for the sake of affiliate tracking and for remembering users when they return to the site. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. You won't be able to login into password protected areas of the site. 

### 3rd Party Tracking

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use both session ID and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. 

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie customer or user personally identifiable information to the information gathered. 

## Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@adlandpro.com. 

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of AdlandPro.com. If you submit personally identifiable information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit. 

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Webmail

We provide the opportunity for users to create a free email account on freemail.adlandpro.com. Personal information provided in this area is governed by the Everyone.net privacy policy <http://www.everyone.net/main/html/p_policy.html>. We only have access to first name, last name and email address created, for account management purposes. 

## Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please [contact us](http://www.adlandpro.com/ContactUs.aspx)

## Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](http://www.adlandpro.com/ContactUs.aspx). Content posted to public community areas is publicly available and AdlandPro.com reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content which is objectionable. 

Softfornet Solutions Ltd.  
23-845 Dakota Street  
Suite 332  
Winnipeg MB R2M 5M3  
Canada
